<resources>
    <string name="onboarding_title">How to use the app</string>
    <string name="onboarding_step_counter">Step %1$d of %2$d</string>
    <string name="onboarding_technology">Technology: %1$s</string>
    <string name="onboarding_back">Back</string>
    <string name="onboarding_next">Next</string>
    <string name="onboarding_enter">Enter</string>
    <string name="onboarding_step_1_title">Compose across the app</string>
    <string name="onboarding_step_1_technology">Jetpack Compose</string>
    <string name="onboarding_step_1_description">Jetpack Compose is the foundation of the entire interface: home, onboarding, drawer, library, article detail, forms, and shared components. The app avoids XML and builds each screen with reusable composables, declarative state, and a consistent visual shell.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_step_1_hint">The top-right avatar opens the drawer and reflects the Compose approach well: navigation, state, visual hierarchy, and reusable components handled from a declarative UI.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_step_2_title">Read articles</string>
    <string name="onboarding_step_2_technology">Retrofit</string>
    <string name="onboarding_step_2_description">The technical library is designed to show service consumption with Retrofit. Although the backend is currently mocked inside the app, the flow uses a real HTTP client, repository, and data parsing as if it talked to an external API.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_step_2_hint">From the home screen, tap the “Read articles” FAB to trigger the remote load and browse the content received by Retrofit.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_step_3_title">User CRUD</string>
    <string name="onboarding_step_3_technology">Room</string>
    <string name="onboarding_step_3_description">The user CRUD exists to show local persistence with Room. Create, edit, list, and delete operations are stored in the device database and reappear when reopening the app.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_step_3_hint">Use “Create user”, “User list”, and “Edit active user” to go through the full Room-persisted flow.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_step_4_title">Technologies used</string>
    <string name="onboarding_step_4_technology">Modern Android stack</string>
    <string name="onboarding_step_4_description">The app integrates Jetpack Compose, Material 3, Navigation Compose, ViewModel, Coroutines, Flow, Hilt, Retrofit, OkHttp, Moshi, Room, Coil, Timber, Kotlinx Serialization, Compose Richtext, and LeakCanary, plus automated tests built with JUnit, kotlinx-coroutines-test, ActivityScenario, UiAutomator, Espresso, and Compose UI Test.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_step_4_hint">This step summarizes the full stack behind the UI, navigation, local data, mocked network layer, DI, observability, memory diagnostics, and automated validation.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_step_5_title">App architecture</string>
    <string name="onboarding_step_5_technology">MVVM and modularization</string>
    <string name="onboarding_step_5_description">The app is organized with an MVVM architecture and module boundaries. The Compose UI observes state exposed by ViewModel, use cases encapsulate concrete operations, and repositories connect the logic with Room, assets, and the mocked remote layer.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_step_5_hint">The main decision was to avoid overengineering: each feature stays isolated, `core` holds shared pieces, and the structure can grow business rules without mixing navigation, UI, and data access.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_demo_open_drawer">Avatar and drawer</string>
    <string name="onboarding_demo_avatar_label">GM</string>
    <string name="onboarding_demo_view_articles">Read articles</string>
    <string name="onboarding_demo_user_create">Create user</string>
    <string name="onboarding_demo_user_list_edit">List and edit</string>
    <string name="onboarding_demo_stack_title">Core stack</string>
    <string name="onboarding_demo_stack_line_1">UI: Compose, Material 3, and Navigation Compose</string>
    <string name="onboarding_demo_stack_line_2">Data: Room, Retrofit, OkHttp, and Moshi</string>
    <string name="onboarding_demo_stack_line_3">Support: Hilt, Flow, Coil, Timber, Serialization, and LeakCanary</string>
    <string name="onboarding_demo_stack_line_4">Tests: JUnit, coroutines-test, ActivityScenario, UiAutomator, Espresso, and Compose UI Test</string>
    <string name="onboarding_demo_architecture_title">How it is organized</string>
    <string name="onboarding_demo_architecture_line_1">MVVM: Compose renders state and ViewModel owns screen logic.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_demo_architecture_line_2">Modules: `app` composes, `feature` implements flows, and `core` shares models, data, and UI.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_demo_architecture_line_3">Use cases: make each operation explicit and decouple UI from repositories.</string>
    <string name="onboarding_demo_architecture_line_4">Decision: scale with clear boundaries without turning the app ceremonial.</string>
</resources>
